mediashower.com 2016-06-22

# Media Shower: Content Writing, Article Writing Services, and Blog Writers

**MEDIA SHOWER, INC. PRIVACY POLICY**

Media Shower, Inc. ("us," "we" "our") has created this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to ensure the confidence of users ("you" or "your") of and to the MediaShower.com website (the "Website"), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. All references herein to Media Shower, inc. or the Website shall mean and include Media Shower, Inc., a Massachusetts corporation that operates the MediaShower.com Website and provides the services therein, and all parents, subsidiaries and affiliates thereof and their respective officers, directors, employees and agents, and any successors and assigns of any of the foregoing.

The Website is offered and made available only to users 18 years of age or older. If you are not yet 18 years old, please discontinue using the Website immediately, or if, for any reason, you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the features, activities and services that require you to provide your Personal Information (as defined below).

This Privacy Policy is a part of the terms and conditions which are set forth in our Terms of Service. Both this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service agreement are legally binding on all you and all other users. Your use and continued participation on the Website indicate your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of information, including your Personal Information, as described below.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Keeping the Personal Information you share with us on the Website secure and ensuring your understanding of how we collect, use, disclose and maintain your Personal Information is important to us. We maintain reasonable physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information and while no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we have used and will continue to use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the protection of your Personal Information. Nonetheless, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any Personal Information you transmit to us or from the Website, and you do so at your own risk.

**1\. Types of Information Collected**

a. _Traffic Data Collected_. We automatically track and collect the following information when you visit our Website, including your: (i) IP address; (ii) domain server; (iii) type of computer; and (iv) type of web browser (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Website.

b. _Personal Information Collected_. In order for you to access certain premium services and/or to purchase products that we may offer via the Website, we may require you to provide us with information that personally identifies you (together, "Personal Information"). Personal Information may include: (i) contact data (such as your name, mailing, billing and e-mail addresses, telephone number and date of birth); (ii) financial data (such as your account or credit card number); and (iii) demographic data (such as your zip code, age, gender, nationality and income). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages in chat rooms, participate in bulletin boards or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communication also may be collected as Personal Information.

It is your responsibility to give us current, complete, truthful and accurate Personal Information and keep it up to date. We assume no liability or responsibility for incorrect, incomplete or false Personal Information.

**2\. Uses and Sharing of Information Collected**

a. _Personal Information_. We may use contact data to send you information about our company or our products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary. We may use your financial data to verify your qualifications for certain products or services and to bill you for products and services. We may use your demographic data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website, including the display of content that we think might be of interest to you according to your preferences.

We may share demographic data with advertisers and other third parties, including disclosure to advertisers and sponsors of our contests and sweepstakes in which you participate. We may share contact data with other companies who may want to send you information about their products or services. If you do not want us to share your contact data with any third parties, please contact us. In the event your Personal Information is being sold, rented and/or shared with any third party, we will use good faith efforts to post a notice on the Website clearly stating that the information is so being used and/or give you the opportunity to opt out of such use.

b. _Traffic Data_. We may use Traffic Data to improve the Website, for marketing purposes, and to analyze usage of the Website.

c. _Targeted Advertising_. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.

**3\. User Choice Regarding Collection, Use and Distribution of Personal Information**

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Website; however, you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Website that require your Personal Information. If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us or from some of our partners, you may select the appropriate "opt-out" option each time we ask you for Personal Information.

**4\. Cookies**

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. Cookies collect data regarding a user's visits to the Website; this data is stored in aggregate form. We may use cookies to, among other things, track repeat visits to the Website and the sites of our partners, determine features you like best, customize content specific to your interests, ensure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, and store your password (if applicable) so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Website.

Although we may track the numbers of visitors to inform us on how best to update the Website and enhance the experience for all visitors, Personal Information is not extracted in this process. We use tracking information on an aggregated basis to help us operate the Website, enhance and improve our service, improve the look of the site and display advertising and marketing information. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie or image tag is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all such devices. This is done through your browser. If you turn cookies off, you may not have access to many features at the Website that make your Internet experience more efficient and enjoyable, and some of our other services may not function properly.

The Website may contain advertisements, references and links to other web sites and organizations. We may also use third parties to display or serve advertising on the Website. Often these third-party advertisers employ cookie and web bug technologies to measure advertising effectiveness. You should be aware that different rules might apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your information by third parties in connection with their advertisements, promotions and other web sites you encounter on the Internet. The use of such technology by these third parties is within their control and not ours. Even if we have a relationship with a third party, we do not control their site(s) or their policies and practices regarding your information.

**5\. Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will NOT share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or defend our interests; or (c) enforce our Terms of Use or applicable law. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers. We provide you with the capability to transmit you Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.

**6\. Lost or Stolen Information**

You must promptly notify us if your credit card, user name and/or password (if applicable) is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such an event, we will cancel that credit card number, user name and/or password and update our records accordingly.

**7\. Other Limits to Your Privacy; Other Sites**

The Website contains links to other sites on the Internet. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, actions or the content of such sites or the third parties that control such sites. We suggest contacting the parties controlling such sites or accessing their online policies for the relevant information about their data collection and privacy policy practices. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions directly of them in this regard.

We may also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed by you in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over the use of these areas and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information. You disclosure of such information may prompt the delivery of unsolicited messages from others. Remember, you are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your user name and password (if applicable), and you are solely responsible for your activity, behavior, use and conduct on the Website and for any use of the Website or any other activity or conduct in connection with the Website by others who may use your user name and password, unless and until you notify of us that such information has been misappropriated, compromised or stolen.

**8\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website.

Last updated January 1, 2012
